Becker, Frank J.; Papers apap224
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Legislative Files, 1953-1964; Undated; 3; 2.4 cubic ft.
  - Introduced January 18, 1963, H.R. 2359, Relief of Demetrios Hasapoglou, 1963-1964 (Box 3 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 14)
  - Introduced January 21, 1963, H. Con. Res. 49, Prayer in UN, Undated (Box 3 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 15)
  - Introduced January 24, 1963, H.R. 2462, Amend-Air Traffic at Idlewild Airport (Box 3 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 16)
  - Introduced January 24, 1963, H.R. 2463, Noise Abatement Research (Idlewild, etc.), 1963-1964 (Box 3 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 17)
  - Introduced January 24, 1963, H.R. 2464, Flight Restrictions with Respect to Aircraft Operating from Certain Airports (Box 3 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 18)
  - Introduced January 24, 1963, H.R. 2551, Deduction Income Tax Transportation Expenses to and from Work (Box 3 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 19)
  - Introduced January 24, 1963, H. Res. 164, Captive Nations Week (Box 3 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 20)
  - Introduced February 21, 1963, H.R. 3923, Commissioned Officers - Retention in an active Status While Employed as Technicians, 1963-1964 (Box 3 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 21)
  - Introduced May 23, 1963, H. Res. 363, To Create a Select Committee on Fiscal Organization and Procedures (Box 3 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 22)
  - Introduced July 24, 1963, H.R. 7754, For the Relief of Hanna Wiernicka (Box 3 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 23)
- Congressional Record and Related Materials, 1958-1964; 4; 2.6 cubic ft.
  Arranged chronologically.
  This series contains copies of the Congressional Record including remarks by or about Frank Becker or of interest to him, such as prayer in schools. Sometimes the entire copy of the Congressional Record appears in the folder, while other times there is just a clipping. In addition, there is supplemental correspondence in some files. Please note the numbers in the folder titles refer to the page number of the remarks of interest.
  - Reprints from Congressional Record, Democrat-Confusion-Hysteria and Politics, 1958 April 22 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 1)
  - Reprints from Congressional Record, Establishing Rules of Interpretation for Fed. Courts Involving Doctrine of Fed. Preemption, 1958 July 17 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 2)
  - FJB Congressional Record Inserts, 1958-1960 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 3)
  - Reprints from Congressional Record, The Safety and Welfare of the U.S., 1959 March 18 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 4)
  - Congressional Record Remarks, 1959 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 5)
  - Congressional Record Remarks, General Correspondence, 1959 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 6)
  - Reprints from Congressional Record, Where is the Justice, 1960 May 11 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 7)
  - Congressional Record Remarks, 1960 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 8)
  - Congressional Record Remarks, General Correspondence, 1960 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 9)
  - Congressional Remarks, Nazi Rally, General Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 10)
  - Congressional Remarks, Nazi Rally, 1960-1962 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 11)
  - Congressional Record Remarks, 1961 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 12-13)
  - Congressional Remarks, General Correspondence, 1961 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 14-16)
  - Reprints from Congressional Record, Citizenship Education in Our Time, 1962 March 26 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 17)
  - Congressional Record Remarks, 1962 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 18-19)
  - Congressional Remarks, General Correspondence, 1962 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 20-21)
  - Remarks, BM McKelway, Citizens' Crime Comm. Dinner, Dec 10, 1962, PA75-76, 1963 January 14 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 22)
  - "Kings Point- The Story of the U.S. Merchant Marine Academy" P A253, 4, 1963 January 24 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 23)
  - "Visit of Betan Court to the U.S." P 975, 1963 January 24 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 24)
  - "The Economic Situation" P 1741, 1963 February 05 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 25)
  - "Seizure of American Investors' Property in Venezuela" P A831, 1963 February 21 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 26)
  - "Why Not Get Down to the Facts" P A935, 936, 1963 February 25 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 27)
  - "Committee on the Un-Am. Activities: Res (HRes 249) making approp." P 2907, 1963 February 27 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 28)
  - "Tax Reduction and Tax Reform" P 2884, 1963 February 27 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 29)
  - "Dialog on the Problems of the National Economy" P 3223, 3224, 1963 March 04 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 30)
  - "Presidential Mistakes, Rep. Allger's Wash. Reprt" P A1151, 1152, 1963 March 04 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 31)
  - "Extension of Draft Law" P 3724, 3725, 3729, 3735, 3738, 1963 March 11 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 32)
  - "Congressmen Who Cheat" P 4658, 1963 March 28 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 33)
  - "Policy of Inaction Against Cuba" P 5480, 1963 April 04 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 34)
  - "Supplemental Appropriation Bill, 1963" P 5706, 5707, 1963 April 09 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 35)
  - Nuclear Submarine, "The Thresher" P 6017, 1963 April 11 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 36)
  - "Pan American Day" P 6003, 6004, 1963 April 11 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 37)
  - The Motion Picture "GO GO" P A2471, 2472, 1963 April 24 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 38)
  - "Health Professions Educ. Assistance Act of 1963" P 6523, 1963 April 24 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 39)
  - "Honorable Emanuel Celler Birthday Tribute" P 7356, 1963 May 06 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 40)
  - "Crime in Washington" P 7357, 7358, 1963 May 06 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 41)
  - "Mr. Becker's Blackout" P 7682, 7683, 1963 May 09 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 42)
  - " The Inequities of Social Security-What You May Not Know" P 7695, 7696, 1963 May 09 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 43)
  - "U.S Gift Aids Wide Sex Study" P A3244, 1963 May 23 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 44)
  - "Migrant Workers Bill-Extend Farm Labor Program" P 9280, 1963 May 29 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 45)
  - "Legislative Branch Appropriation Bill-1964)" P 10040, 1963 June 11 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 46)
  - "Area Redevelopment Act Amendments of 1963" P 10096, 1963 June 12 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 47)
  - "Mount Carmel, Center and Hospital for Alcoholics" P A3804, 3805, 3806, 1963 June 13 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 48)
  - "Constitutional Amendment to Permit Prayer in Public Schools" P 10557, 1963 June 19 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 49)
  - "Charges by Mr. McNamara" P 10755, 1963 June 24 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 50)
  - "Increase in District of Columbia Borrowing Authority" P 10773, 1963 June 24 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 51)
  - "Dept. of Defense Appropriations Bill-1964" P 11105, 11106, 1963 June 26 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 52)
  - "Supreme Court Decision on Prayer", 1963 July 09 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 53)
  - "Safety Standards for Automobile Seat Belts" P 11659, 1963 July 10 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 54)
  - "Prayer in Public Schools" P 11773, 1963 July 11 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 55)
  - Tribute to the Honorable Carl Vinson" P 12008, 1963 July 16 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 56)
  - "The High Court and the Court on High" P A4462, 1963 July 16 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 57)
  - "Discharge Petition on Prayer in Public Schools" P 12076, 1963 July 17 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 58)
  - "Private Bill-Hanna Wiernicka", 1963 July 24 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 59)
  - "Prayer" P 12623, 1963 July 25 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 60)
  - "Prayer", 1963 July 31 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 61)
  - "NASA Appropriations Bill" P 13126, 1963 August 01 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 62)
  - "Prayer in Our Public Schools" P A4987, 4988, 1963 August 06 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 63)
  - "DC Business Bill on Crime, Prevention, and Penalties" P 13927, 13928, 13945, 13946, 1963 August 12 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 64)
  - "Methodists Warns Against Secularists Efforts" P A5107, 1963 August 12 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 65)
  - "Set of Goals of the Am. Assn. for the Advancement of Atheism" P A5156, 5157, 1963 August 14 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 66)
  - Prayer in the Public Schools" P 14417, 1963 August 19 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 67)
  - "Supreme Court decision threatenseradication of religion from gov't" P A5263, 5264, 1963 August 19 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 68)
  - "Foreign Assistance Act of 1963, P 14759, 1963 August 22 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 69)
  - "Prayer and Bible Reading in Public Schools" P 15833, 1963 September 10 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 70)
  - "Civil Defense", 1963 September 17 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 71)
  - "Senator Engle" P 16433, 1963 September 18 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 72)
  - "ACLU Protests US Chaplains" P A5883, 1963 September 18 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 73)
  - "Deplorable Philosophy of the News Media" P 16434, 1963 September 18 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 74)
  - "Prayer-Newport, KY High School", 1963 September 19 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 75)
  - "Internal Revenue Code of 1954" P 17137, 17138, 1963 September 25 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 76)
  - "Are You A Patriot"- Art Buchwald, P A6075, 6076, 1963 September 26 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 77)
  - "Continuing Appropriations for Certain Depts of Govt" P 19341-3, 19347, 19348, 1963 October 01 (Box 1 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 78)
  - "Independent Offices-Appropriations Bill, 1964" P 18263, 1963 October 10 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 1)
  - "Crime in the City of Washington" P 18566, 1963 October 15 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 2)
  - "Inaction of Congress" P 18573, 1963 October 15 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 3)
  - "National Day of Prayer" P 18631, 18632, 1963 October 16 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 4)
  - "Support for Prayer Amendment, Rev Geo. T Cook" P A6535, 6537, 1963 October 17 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 5)
  - " TITO (Madam Nhu) P 18800, 1963 October 17 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 6)
  - "Government Harassment of Business" P 18992, 1963 October 22 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 7)
  - Jet Age Marks Fifth Anniversary, 1963 October 24 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 8)
  - "Prayer in Public Schools and" P 19223, 1963 October 24 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 9)
  - "Continuing Appropriations for Certain Depts of Govt" P 19341-3, 19347, 19348, 1963 October 28 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 10)
  - "Legislative Business on Tuesday, November 5, 1963" P 19578, 1963 October 30 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 11)
  - "Armed Forces Participation in International Sports" P 20940, 1963 November 18 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 12)
  - "To Amend the Arms Control and Disarmament Act" P 21421, 1963 November 20 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 13)
  - " Statement on J Edgar Hoover and Mrs. Hardy's Petition" P 21454, 1963 November 20 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 14)
  - "Kennedy Tribute", 1963 December 05 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 15)
  - "Civil Rights and Demagoguery", 1963 December 10 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 16)
  - "Retired Officers of the Army, Navy, and Air Force" P 23600, 1963 December 17 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 17)
  - "Prayer" P 23719, 1963 December 18 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 18)
  - "Remarks by Mr Corman (California), 1963 December 21 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 19)
  - "American Legion-Prayer" P A44, 1964 January 08 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 20)
  - "Massachusetts Citizens for Prayer (Father Howes)" P 402, A162, 1964 January 14 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 21)
  - Eulogy to the Late Congressman Howard H Baker P 551, 1964 January 16 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 22)
  - 46th Anniversary of the Independence of the Ukraine, P 900, 1964 January 22 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 23)
  - Passage of H.R. 8937 for the Relief of Retired Officers of Army, Navy, Air Force P 565, 1964 January 20 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 24)
  - Personal Announcement, Name Correction P 877, 1964 January 22 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 25)
  - "Venezuela Sulphur Corporation (Ben Dowd) P 896, 897, 1964 January 23 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 26)
  - Remarks about Ed Foreman P 1200, 1964 January 28 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 27)
  - "The Donkey Looked Too Self-Righteous", Long Island PressLetter, P A420, 1964 January 31 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 28)
  - "On Enactment and Debate of Civil Rights Bill" P 1477, 1964 January 31 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 29)
  - "On Enactment and Debate on Civil Rights Bill" P 1525, 1964 February 01 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 30)
  - VFW Proposes Naval Control in Panama Canal Crises, 1964 February 01 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 31)
  - Civil Rights Vote In House, 1964 February 10 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 32)
  - Lithuanian Independence Day P 2873, 1964 February 17 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 33)
  - "Longshoremen Refuse to Load Wheat on Ships" P 2835, 1964 February 17 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 34)
  - Harry Kalich, P 3031, 1964 February 19 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 35)
  - "The American Legion Supports Prayer in Public Schools and Places", 1964 February 20 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 36)
  - "Military Procurement" P 3076, 3077, 3078, P 3089, 3098, 3099, 1964 February 20 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 37)
  - "Prayer-Congressman Celler (Letter)" P 3101, 3102, 1964 February 20 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 38)
  - "Taxation" P 3443, 3444, 1964 February 25 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 39)
  - "Prayer Constitutional Amendment" P 3421, 1964 February 25 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 40)
  - "Prayer-Celler" P 3517, 1964 February 26 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 41)
  - "International Development Assn" P 3515, 1964 February 26 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 42)
  - "International Development Assn" P 3727, 1964 February 27 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 43)
  - "Defense Procurement-Research and Development" P 3865, 1964 March 02 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 44)
  - "A Woman Writer takes A Critical Look at America- Mrs Mae Craig" A990, 1964 March 02 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 45)
  - "Armed Services" P 4518, 1964 March 09 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 46)
  - "Prayer In Public Schools" P 4690, 1964 March 10 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 47)
  - "Tribute to Congressman Frank J Becker (The Tablet)" P 5327, 1964 March 17 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 48)
  - "Armed Services" P 5373, 1964 March 18 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 49)
  - "Mellowing Atheism" P A1408, 1964 March 23 (Box 2 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 50)
  - "Civil Rights" P 7484, 1964 April 13 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 1)
  - "Pan American Day" P 7582, 1964 April 14 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 2)
  - "Prayer and Bible Reading (Sisk)" P 8914, 1964 April 27 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 3)
  - "Prayer-Chet Doyle" P A2784, 1964 May 26 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 4)
  - "Prayer-Celler" P 11583, 1964 May 26 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 5)
  - "Prayer (Hicksville, LI, School)" P 11583-11584, 1964 May 26 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 6)
  - "Prayer Memorial Day Address, Chet Doyle" PA2797, 1964 May 26 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 7)
  - "Judiciary Committee (Funds) P 12027, 1964 June 02 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 8)
  - "Prayer, LI Res. Reg. Geo. T Cook, Greg Dixon Letter (Baptists)" P 12047, 1964 June 02 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 9)
  - "Knights of Columbus, Conn. Prayer Resolution" P 12066, 1964 June 03 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 10)
  - "Establishment Godless Republic Not Meant for US (Widener) " P A3072, 1964 June 08 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 11)
  - "Prayer-Full Gospel Tabernacle, Massapequa, LI" P 12579, 1964 June 09 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 12)
  - "Prayer, Bible Reading in Public Schools, David Lawrence" P 12744, 12745, 1964 June 10 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 13)
  - "Pay Raise" P 13039, 1964 June 11 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 14)
  - "Prayer Article-Foreign Student" P A3198, 1964 June 15 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 15)
  - "Woodmere Elementary School Contribution (Alaska)" P 13252, 1964 June 15 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 16)
  - "Letter to Congressman" P 13262, 1964 June 15 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 17)
  - "Overseas GI Wants Prayer In School" A3252, 1964 June 16 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 18)
  - "NJ Bldg and Construction Council PetitionRestore Prayer" P 13580, 1964 June 17 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 19)
  - "Boston-Canon, School Prayer Amendment" P A3279, 1964 June 17 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 20)
  - "The Constitution and Pornography, People not Court Make Laws" P A3279, 1964 June 17 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 21)
  - "Prayer (Lawyers), Prof Charles E. Rice" P 13580, 1964 June 17 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 22)
  - "The Policeman's Parting Shot-Insp Chas H Glucksman" P A3339, 1964 June 18 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 23)
  - "School Prayer Endorsement, Farm Bureau Council 14-A, Ohio" P A3344, 1964 June 18 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 24)
  - "Civil Defense (Alaska)" P 14144, 1964 June 22 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 25)
  - "What About This Filibuster" P 14450, 1964 June 24 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 26)
  - "National Catholic Youth Res." P 15007, 1964 June 30 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 27)
  - "Men of Decision Need Our Prayers- Bishop Fulton J Sheen" P 15076, 1964 July 01 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 28)
  - "Prayer, Rev. Jos Montagna" P 15076, 1964 July 01 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 29)
  - "Open Bible Standard Churches Endorse Prayerin Public Schools" P 15076, 1964 July 01 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 30)
  - "Women of America, For God's Sake, Awake Mrs Regan" P 15428, 1964 July 02 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 31)
  - "Captive Nations Week, July 12-18, 1964" P A3688, 1964 July 02 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 32)
  - "Prayer, Rice Answers NCWC, Prof. Charles E Rice" P 15429, 1964 July 02 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 33)
  - "Modify Immigration Laws, Re: Congressman John W. Wydler" P 16654, 1964 July 28 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 34)
  - "Prayer and Bible Reading in Public Schools" P 16667, 1964 July 29 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 35)
  - "Crime Proves Need For Religious Training" P A4002, 1964 July 30 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 36)
  - "2 Citizens of Vietnam, US Military Academy" P 17305, 1964 August 04 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 37)
  - "Prayer and Bible Reading In School, Rev. Claud L Asbury, Baptist" P A4161, 1964 August 06 (Box 3 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 38)
  - "Prayer and Bible Reading in Schools (J Goodloe Jackson, Allegany" P A4156, 1964 August 06 (Box 4 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 1)
  - "Becker Challenges Celler (Prayer) P 18363, 1964 August 11 (Box 4 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 2)
  - "American Legions Position on Prayer" P A4269, 1964 August 12 (Box 4 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 3)
  - "Who Is Tampering With the 1st Amendment? Rev. Bedsole (Baptist)" P A4306, 1964 August 13 (Box 4 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 4)
  - "State Department Again Fails American Investors in Venezuela" P 19098, 1964 August 14 (Box 4 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 5)
  - "News Abroad but Not at Home (Ben Dowd, London Express)", 1964 August 18 (Box 4 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 6)
  - "Government Must Help Moral Uplifting (Cardinal Spellman)" P 19703, 1964 August 19 (Box 4 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 7)
  - "Dr. Lowry's Statement before Judiciary Committee Prayer, "A Constitutional Prayer Amendment"" P A4354-4357, 1964 September 01 (Box 4 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 8)
  - "Walter Lippmann and his Predictions" P 21721, 1964 September 22 (Box 4 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 9)
  - "Prayer in Public Schools, Questionnaire to Catholic Bishops" P 23249, 1964 October 03 (Box 4 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 10)
  - "Tribute to Hon. Frank J Becker, Hon. Olin E Teague" P A5315, 1964 October 12 (Box 4 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 11)
  - "Tribute to Hon. Frank J Becker, Hon. W. J Bryan Dorn" P A5479, 1964 October 20 (Box 4 (4-Congressional Record), Folder 12)